ILGWU. Research Department wages and hours files, 5780/148
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Divisions Special Industry Committee Number 40D, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  Public Hearing for Needlework and Fabricated Textile Products Industry in Puerto Rico. Exhibits, Report, Findings of Fact, Recommendations, and Wage Order. Volume 3
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contract Division Special Industry Committee 48A, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  Public Hearings for Needlework and Fabricated Textile Products Industry in Puerto Rico. Exhibits, Report, Findings of Fact, Recommendations, Wage Orders. Volume 2
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 22E, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  Public Hearing for Needlework and Fabricated Textile Products Industry in Puerto Rico. Volume 4
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 40D, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  Public Hearing for Needlework and Fabricated Textile Products Industry in Puerto Rico. Volume 2. July
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 46B, 1959-1960 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  Public Hearings for Men's and Boys' Clothing and Related Products Industry in Puerto Rico. Exhibits, Report, Findings of Fact, Recommendations, and Wage Orders. Volume 2
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 48A, 1960 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  Public Hearing for Needlework and Fabricated Textile Products Industry in Puerto Rico. Hearings. Volume 1
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 46A, 1960 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  Public Hearings for Corsets, Brassieres, and Allied Garments Industry in Puerto Rico. Hearings. Volume 1
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 40E, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  Public Hearing for Sweater and Knit Swimwear Industry in Puerto Rico. Volume 2, Pages 277-478. July
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 56C, 1962 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  Public Hearings for Sweater and Knit Swimwear Industry in Puerto Rico. Exhibit 7-Appeal of the Sweater and Knit Swimwear Industry. Volume 3
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 46B, 1960 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  Public Hearings for Men's and Boys' Clothing and Related Products Industry in Puerto Rico. Hearings. Volume 1
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 56A, 1962 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  Public Hearings for Women's and Children's Underwear and Women's Blouse Industry in Puerto Rico. Hearings. Volume 1
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 40E, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  Public Hearing for Sweater and Knit Swimwear Industry in Puerto Rico. Volume 1, Pages 1-276
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 40D, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  Public Hearing for Needlework and Fabricated Textile Products Industry in Puerto Rico.Volume 1, Pages 1-302
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 81B, 1966-1968 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  Public Hearings for Corsets, Brassieres, and Allied Garments Industry in Puerto Rico. Exhibits. Volume 3
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 40C, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  Public Hearings for Children's Dress and Related Products Industry in Puerto Rico. Volume 1, Pages 1-260
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 40A, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  Public Hearings for Handkerchief, Square Scarf, and Art Linen Industry in Puerto Rico. Exhibits, Report, Findings of Fact, Recommendations, and Wage Order. Volume 2
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contract Divisions Special Industry Committee Number 46A, 1959-1960 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  Public Hearings for Corsets, Brassieres, and Allied Garments Industry in Puerto Rico. Exhibits, Report, Findings of Fact, Recommendations, and Wage Order. Volume 2
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 56A, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  Public Hearings for Women's and Children's Underwear and Women's Blouse Industry in Puerto Rico. Exhibits, Report, Findings of Fact, Recommendations, and Wage Order. Volume 2
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 56B, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  Public Hearings for Handkerchief, Scarf, and Art Linen Industry in Puerto Rico. Exhibits, Report, Findings of Fact, Recommendations, and Wage Order. Volume 2
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 48E, 1960 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  Public Hearings for Sweater and Knit Swimwear Industry in Puerto Rico. Exhibits, Report, Finding of Fact, Recommendations, and Wage Order. Volume 2
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 48B, 1960 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  Public Hearings for Handkerchief, Square Scarf, and Art Linen Industry in Puerto Rico. Exhibits, Report, Finding of Fact, Recommendations, and Wage Order. Volume 2
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 48D, 1960 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  Public Hearing for Children's Dress and Related Products Industry in Puerto Rico. Exhibits, Report, Finding of Fact, Recommendations, and Wage Order. Volume 2
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 58A, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  Public Hearings for the Needlework and Fabricated Textile Products Industry in Puerto Rico. Exhibits, Reports, Findings of Fact, Recommendations, and Wage Order. Volume 2
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 58B, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  Public Hearings for the Children's Dress and Related Industry in Puerto Rico. Exhibits, Report, Findings of Fact, Recommendations, and Wage Order. Volume 2
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 68C, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  Public Hearings for the Sweater and Knit Swimwear Industry in Puerto Rico. Exhibits, Report, Findings of Fact, Recommendations, and Wage Order. Volume 2
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 68B, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 68B, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  Public Hearings for Handkerchief, Scarf, and Art Linen Industry in Puerto Rico. Hearings. Volume 1
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 57A, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 57B, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  Public Hearings for the Men's and Boys' Clothing and Related Products Industry in Puerto Rico. Exhibits, Report, Findings of Fact, Recommendations, and Wage Order.
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 57A, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contract Division Review Committee Number 12, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  Public Hearing for the Handkerchief, Scarf, and Art Linen Industry in Puerto Rico. Exhibits, Report, Findings of Fact, Recommendations, and Wage Order. Volume 2
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Review Committee Number 6B, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  Public Hearing for Women's and Children's Underwear and Women's Blouse Industry in Puerto Rico. Exhibits, Report, Findings of Fact, Recommendations, and Wage Order. Volume 3
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Review Committee Number 6A, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  Public Hearings for Sweater and Knit Swimwear Industry in Puerto Rico. Exhibits, Report, Findings of Fact, Recommendations, and Wage Order. Volume 3
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Review Committee Number 6B, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  Public Hearing for Women's and Children's Underwear and Women's Blouse Industry in Puerto Rico. Appeals. Volume 1
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Review Committee Number 6B, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  Public Hearings for Women's and Children's Underwear and Women's Blouse Industry in Puerto Rico. Hearings. Volume 2
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Review Committee Number 9, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  Public Hearing for the Handkerchief, Scarf, and Art Linen Industry in Puerto Rico. Exhibits, Report, Findings of Fact, Recommendations, and Wage Orders. Volume 2
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Review Committee Number 6A, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  Public Hearing for Sweater and Knit Swimwear Industry in Puerto Rico. Appeals. Volume 1
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Review Committee Number 12, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Review Committee Number 6C, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  Public Hearings for Handkerchief, Scarf, and Art Linen Industry in Puerto Rico. Hearing. Volume 2
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Review Committee Number 6C, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  Public Hearing for Handkerchief, Scarf, and Art Linen Industry in Puerto Rico. Exhibits, Report, Findings of Fact, Recommendations, and Wage Order. Volume 3
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Review Committee Number 2C, 1960-1961 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Review Committee Number 2A, 1960-1961 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  Public Hearings for Sweater and Knit Swimwear Industry in Puerto Rico. Exhibits, Report, Findings of Fact, Recommendations, and Wage Orders. Volume 3
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 58A, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  Public Hearings for Children's Dress and Related Products Industry in Puerto Rico. Hearings. Volume 1
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 68A, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  Public Hearing for Women's and Children's Underwear and Women's Blouse Industry in Puerto Rico. Exhibits, Report, Findings of Fact, Recommendations, and Wage Order. Volume 2
- Prehearing Statement of the Sweater and Knit Swimwear Industry in Puerto Rico, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  Review Committee 68C
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 68A, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 56C, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  Public Hearings for Sweater and Knit Swimwear Industry in Puerto Rico. Hearings. Volume 1
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 81B, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 58A, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  Public Hearings for Needlework and Fabricated Textile Products Industry in Puerto Rico. Hearings. Volume 1
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 56B, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 48B, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  Public Hearing for Handkerchief, Square Scarf, and Art Linen Industry in Puerto Rico. Hearings. Volume 1
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 48D, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 48E, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 48C, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  Public Hearings for Women's and Children's Underwear and Women's Blouse and Neckwear Industry in Puerto Rico. Hearings. Volume 1
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 56C, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  Public Hearings for Sweater and Knit Swimwear Industry in Puerto Rico. Exhibits, Report, Findings of Fact, Recommendations, and Wage Order. Volume 2
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 69C, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  Public Hearings for Children's Dress and Related Products Industry in Puerto Rico. Hearing. Volume 1
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Divisions Special Industry Committee Number 69C, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 15)
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Divisions Special Industry Committee Number 69B, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  Public Hearing for Corsets, Brassieres, and Allied Garments Industry in Puerto Rico. Hearing. Volume 1
- U.S. Wage and Hour Division Industry Committee Number 113B, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  Public Hearings for the Children's Dress and Related Products Industry in Puerto Rico. Exhibits, Report, Findings of Fact, Recommendations, and Wage Order. Volume 2
- U.S. Wage and Hour Division Industry Committee Number 113C, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  Public Hearings for the Women's Outerwear, Needlework, and Miscellaneous Fabricated Textile Products Industry in Puerto Rico. Exhibits, Report, Findings of Fact, Recommendations, and Wage Order. Volume 2
- U.S. Wage and Hour Division Industry Committee Number 128B, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Review Committee Number 3B, 1961 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Request for Review of PR Minimum Wages, Underwear and Blouse Industry, 1961 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Review Committee Number 2A, 1961 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  Public Hearings for Sweater and Knit Swimwear Industry in Puerto Rico. Exhibit 7- Appeal of Sweater and Knit Swimwear Industry. Volume 4
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Review Committee Number 2A, 1961 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  Public Hearings for Sweater and Knit Swimwear Industry in Puerto Rico. Hearings. Volume 2, pages 339-613
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Review Committee Number 2A, 1961 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  Public Hearings for Sweater and Knit Swimwear Industry in Puerto Rico. Hearings. Volume 1, Pages 1-338
- Request for Review of PR Minimum Wages, Knitgoods, 1961 (Box 18, Folder 9)
- U.S. Wage and Hour Division Industry Committee Number 138A, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  Public Hearing for the Women's and Children's Underwear and Women's Blouse Industry in Puerto Rico. Exhibits, Report, Findings of Fact, Recommendations, and Wage Order. Volume 2
- U.S. Wage and Hour Division Industry Committee Number 138A, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  Public Hearing for the Women's and Children's Underwear and Women's Blouse Industry in Puerto Rico. Hearing. Volume 1
- U.S. Wage and Hour Division Industry Committee Number 128C, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 12)
- U.S. Wage and Hour Division Industry Committee Number 128E, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  Public Hearing for the Women's Outerwear, Needlework, and Miscellaneous Fabricated Textile Products Industry in Puerto Rico. Hearing. Volume 1
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Review Committee Number 2B, 1960-1961 (Box 18, Folder 14)
- U.S. Wage and Hour Division Industry Committee Number 128F, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  Public Hearings for the Sweater and Knit Swimwear Industry in Puerto Rico. Hearings. Volume 1
- U.S. Wage and Hour Division Industry Committee Number 113A, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  Public Hearings for the Corsets, Brassieres, and Allied Garments Industry in Puerto Rico. Exhibit7, Part 1. Volume 3
- U.S. Wage and Hour Division Industry Committee Number 128B, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- U.S. Wage and Hour Division Industry Committee Number 128F, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  Public Hearing for the Sweater and Knit Swimwear Industry in Puerto Rico. Exhibits, Report, Findings of Fact, Recommendations, Dissent, and Wage Order. Volume 2
- U.S. Wage and Hour Division Industry Committee Number 128E, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  Public Hearing for the Women's Outerwear, Needlework, and Miscellaneous Fabricated Textile Products Industry in Puerto Rico. Exhibits, Report, Findings of Fact, Recommendations, Dissent, and Wage Order. Volume 2
- U.S. Wage and Hour Division Industry Committee Number 128C, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  Public Hearing for Corsets, Brassieres, and Allied Garments Industry in Puerto Rico. Exhibits, Report, Findings of Fact, Recommendations, and Wage Order. Volume 2
- Request for Review of Puerto Rico Minimum Wages, Handkerchief, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Review Committee Number 2B, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  Public Hearings for Women's and Children's Underwear and Women's Blouse and Neckwear Industry in Puerto Rico. Exhibit 15-Prehearing Statement of Appliqué Inc. Volume 3
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Review Committee Number 2C, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  Public Hearings for Handkerchiefs, Square Scarf, and Art Linen Industry in Puerto Rico. Hearings. Volume 2
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Review Committee Number 6A, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  Public Hearings for Sweater and Knit Swimwear Industry in Puerto Rico. Hearings. Volume 2
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Review Committee Number 6C, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  Public Hearing for Handkerchief, Scarf, and Art Linen industry in Puerto Rico. Appeals. Volume 1
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Review Committee Number 6A, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  Public Hearing for Sweater and Knit Swimwear Industry in Puerto Rico. Exhibit 10. Volume 4
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 75, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 81A, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  Public Hearings for Men's and Boys' Clothing and Related Products Industry in Puerto Rico. Hearings. Volume 2, pages 242-464
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 75, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  Public Hearings for Sweater and Knit Swimwear Industry in Puerto Rico. Hearings, Journal of Proceedings, Executive Session. Volume 1
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 81D, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  Public Hearings for Needlework and Fabricated Textile Products Industry in Puerto Rico. Exhibits, Report, Findings of Fact, Recommendations, and Wage Order. Volume 2
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 81D, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 5)
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 81C, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 6)
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 81B, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  Public Hearings for Corset, Brassieres, and Allied Garments Industry in Puerto Rico. Exhibits. Volume 2
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 69D, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  Public Hearing for Men's and Boys' Clothing Related Products Industry in Puerto Rico. Exhibits, Report, Findings of Fact, Recommendations, and Wage Order. Volume 2
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 69D, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  Public Hearing for Men's and Boys' Clothing and Related Products Industry in Puerto Rico. Hearing. Volume 1
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 69B, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  Public Hearing for Corsets, Brassieres, and Allied Garment Industry in Puerto Rico. Exhibits, Report, Findings of Fact, Recommendations, and Wage Order. Volume 2
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 69A, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  Public Hearing for Needlework and Fabricated Textile Product Industry in Puerto Rico. Exhibits, Noted, Report, Findings of Fact, Recommendations, and Wage Order. Volume 2
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 69A, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  Public Hearing for Needlework and Fabricated Textile Product Industry in Puerto Rico. Hearing. Volume 1
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 81C, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  Public Hearings for Children's Dress and Related Products Industry in Puerto Rico. Exhibits, Report, Findings of Fact, Recommendations, and Wage Order. Volume 2
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 81A, 1969 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  Public Hearings for Men's and Boys' Clothing and Related Products Industry in Puerto Rico. Exhibits, Report, and Wage Order. Volume 3
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 81A, 1969 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  Public Hearings for Men's and Boys' Clothing and Related Products Industry in Puerto Rico. Hearings. Volume 1, pages 1-241
- U.S. Wage and Hour Divisions Special Industry Committee Number 101A, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  Public Hearing for the Corsets, Brassieres, and Allied Garments Industry in Puerto Rico. Hearings. Volume 1
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 75, 1965-1966 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  Public Hearings for Sweater and Knit Swimwear Industry in Puerto Rico. Volume 4
- Prehearing Statement of the Sweater and Knit Swimwear Industry in Puerto Rico, Industry Committee Number 75, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  Volume 3
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 82B, 1969 (Box 21, Folder 6)
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 82B, 1969 (Box 21, Folder 7)
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 82A, 1969 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  Public Hearings for Sweater and Knit Swimwear Industry in Puerto Rico. Pre-Hearing Statement. Volume 3
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 82C, 1969 (Box 21, Folder 9)
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 82A, 1969 (Box 21, Folder 10)
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 82A, 1969 (Box 21, Folder 11)
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 68C, 1964 (Box 21, Folder 12)
- U.S. Wage and Hour and Public Contracts Division Special Industry Committee Number 82C, 1969 (Box 21, Folder 13)
- U.S. Wage and Hour Division Industry Committee Number 102B, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  Public Hearing for the Sweater and Knit Swimwear Industry in Puerto Rico. Exhibits, Report, Findings of Fact, Recommendations, and Wage Order. Volume 2
- U.S. Wage and Hour Division Industry Committee Number 102B, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- U.S. Wage and Hour Division Industry Committee Number 102A, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- U.S. Wage and Hour Division Industry Committee Number 102A, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  Public Hearings for Women's and Children's Underwear for Women's Blouse Industry in Puerto Rico. Hearings. Volume 1
- U.S. Wage and Hour Division Industry Committee Number 101D, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  Public Hearings for Handkerchief, Scarf, and Art Linen Industry. Exhibits, Report, Findings of Fact, Recommendations, and Wage Order. Volume 2
- U.S. Wage and Hour Division Industry Committee Number 101D, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- U.S. Wage and Hour Division Industry Committee Number 101C, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  Public Hearings for Women's Outerwear, Needlework, and Miscellaneous Fabricated Textile Products Industry in Puerto Rico. Exhibits, Report, Findings of Fact, Recommendations, and Wage Order. Volume 2